Guide to the New York Building Congress Records WAG.167
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Administrative Records, 1921-2010
  - City Planning and Development Committee, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Clark, Bradford N. (President), 1958-1962 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Clark, Bradford N. (Public Relations Committee), 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Coletti, Louis J. (President): Proposals, Statements, and Testimony, 1986-1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Collins, John J. (President; Chairman, Council of Presidents), 1969-1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Building Conditions, 1923-1927 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Codes: "Code of Ethics," drafts, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Codes: "Code of Ethics," pamphlets, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Cost-Plus-a-Fixed-Fee and Other Types of Construction Contracts, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Disposal of Construction Wastes, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Old Age Pensions and Insurance, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Old Age Pensions and Insurance: Pension Study, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Relationship between General and Subcontractors, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Reorganization of the New York City Housing Authority, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Revision of Contract between General and Subcontractor, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Trends toward Independent Subcontracts, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Trends toward Independent Subcontracts, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Trends toward Independent Subcontracts, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Committees: Lists, 1934-2007, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Communication and Membership Committee: Agendas, 2002-2007 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Communications Committee, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, circa 1945 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1987, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Constitution and By-Laws Committee, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Constitution and By-Laws Committee, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Constitution and By-Laws Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Construction Controls Committee, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Construction Industry Advancement Program, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Construction Industry Advisory Committee, 1976, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Construction Industry Development Board, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Construction Industry Development Board: Construction Environmental Task Force, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Construction Industry Development Board: Contract with New York Task Force, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Construction Industry Development Board: Creating and Industry Database Task Force, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Construction Industry Practices Committee, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Construction Industry Practices Committee: Recommendations, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Construction Industry Practices Committee: Subcommittee on "Or Equal" Clause, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Council of Business and Labor, 1984-1988 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Council of Business and Labor, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Council of Presidents, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Council of Presidents, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Council of Presidents, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Council of Presidents, Jan-Jun 1979 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Council of Presidents, Jul-Dec 1979 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Council of Presidents, Jan-Aug 1980 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Council of Presidents, Sep-Dec 1980 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Council of Presidents, Jan-May 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Council of Presidents, Jun-Dec 1981 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Council of Presidents, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Council of Presidents, Jan-Mar 1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Council of Presidents, Apr-Jun 1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Council of Presidents, Jul-Sep 1983 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Council of Presidents, Oct-Dec 1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Council of Presidents, Jan-Jun 1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Council of Presidents, Jul-Dec 1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Council of Presidents, Jan-Jun 1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Council of Presidents, Jul-Dec 1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Council of Presidents, Jan-Jun 1986 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Council of Presidents, Jul-Dec 1986 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Council of Presidents, Jan-Jun 1987 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Council of Presidents, Jul-Dec 1987 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Council of Presidents, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Council of Presidents, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Council of Presidents, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Council of Presidents, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Council of Presidents, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Council of Presidents, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Council of Presidents, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Council of Presidents, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Council of Presidents, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Council of Presidents, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Council of Presidents, Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Council of Presidents: Agendas, 2000-2007 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Council of Presidents: Finances, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Council of Presidents: Finances, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Council of Presidents: Host Schedules, 1985-1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Council of Presidents: Legislative Luncheon, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Council of Presidents: Luncheons, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Council of Presidents: Nominating Committee, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Council of Presidents: Nominations, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Council of Presidents: Reorganization, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Council of Presidents: Roster, Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Council of Presidents: Westway Support Campaign, 1981-1986 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Craftsmanship: Certificate of Superior Craftsmanship, circa 1920s (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Craftsmanship: Committee on Recognition of Craftsmanship, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Craftsmanship: Committee on Recognition of Craftsmanship, circa 1920s (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Craftsmanship: General, circa 1920s (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Craftsmanship: "How it is Put into Effect", 1926 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Craftsmanship: Recognition in "Building Age", 1927 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Craftsmanship: "Recognition of Craftsmanship", 1925, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Craftsmanship: "What is a Good Craftsman?", circa 1920s (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Cutler, Robert W. (President), 1964-1969 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Dues Policy Committee, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Economic Development Committee, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Economic Development Committee, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Economic Development Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Economic Development Committee, 2004-2006 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Economic Development Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Economic Development Committee: Agendas, 2000-2007 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Economic Impact Steering Committee, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Edifice: Background, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Education Committee, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Education Committee, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Education Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Education and Healthcare Committee, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Educational Facilities Construction Task Force (Ed Con), 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Energy Committee (I), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Energy Committee (II), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Energy Committee, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Energy Committee, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Energy Committee, 2004-2006 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Energy Committee, 2007-2010 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Energy Committee: Agendas, 2000-2007 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Environmental Committee, 2002-2007 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Environmental Committee: Brownfields Subcommittee, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Environmental Task Force, 1982-1986 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Escalation and Shortages Committee, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Executive Committee, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Executive Committee, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Executive Committee, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Executive Committee, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Executive Committee, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Executive Committee, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Executive Committee, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Executive Committee, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Executive Committee, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Executive Committee, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Executive Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Executive Committee, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee: Agendas, 2000-2007 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Fact Finding Committee, 1930-1931 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Finances, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Finances, 1934-1940 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Finances, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Finances, 1978-1984 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Finances, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Finances, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Finances, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Finances, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Finances, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Finances, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Finances, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Finances, 2007, Undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Finances: Business Expansion Plan, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Finances: Ledger, Burt L. Fenner Memorial Fund, 1926-1959 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Finances: Ledger, General, 1944-1963 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Finances: Ledger, General, 1963-1974 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Finances: Ledger, Luncheons & Outings, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Financial Reports, 1998, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Financial Statements, 1988, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Fire Safety Committee, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Future of the Construction Industry Committee, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Future of the Construction Industry Committee, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Governmental Affairs Committee, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Governmental Affairs Committee, 1976-1983 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Governmental Affairs Committee: New York City Charter Revision, 1975-1988 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Governor's Advisory Committee on the New York City Construction Industry, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Haines, Charles (President), 1962-1972 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Harris, Michael M. (President), 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Healthcare Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Healthcare Committee, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 38a)
  - Hennessey, John F. (President), 1957-1973 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Housing Committee, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Housing Committee, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Insurance and Bonding Committee, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Joint Building Industry Committee on City Contracts, 1952-1955 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Joint Energy Committee (Real Estate Board of New York, NYBC, & Association for a Better New York), 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Land Use Review Committee, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Land Utilization Committee: Land Usage, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Land Utilization Committee: Problems Affecting Housing, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Land Utilization Committee: Research Bulletins, 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Legislative Committee, 1960-1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Committee, 1973, 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 1a)
  - Legislative Committee, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 1b)
  - Legislative Committee, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 1c)
  - Legislative Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Legislative Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Report, 1978-1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Report, 1983-1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Liasion Committee, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Liasion Councils, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Management Committee, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 7a)
  - Membership Applications, 1936, 1951, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Membership Committee, 1955-1958 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Membership Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Membership Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Membership Committee, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Membership Committee, 1986-1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Membership Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Membership Committee, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Membership Committee: Agendas, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Membership Committee: Correspondence, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Membership: Correspondence, 1924, 1978-1996 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Membership Expansion Campaign, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Membership: Invoices, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Membership: Life Members, 1962-1984 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Membership Lists (Yearbook), 1923-1924 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Membership Lists (Yearbook), 1925-1926 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Membership Lists (Yearbook), 1928-1929 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Membership Lists, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Membership Lists, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Membership Lists, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Membership Lists, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Membership Lists, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Membership Lists, 1994-1995, Undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Membership Lists: Officers, 1945, Undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Membership: New Members, 1982-1991 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Membership: New Members, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Membership: New Members, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Membership: New Members, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Membership: New Members, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Membership Packet, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 36a)
  - Membership: Prospect Letters, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Membership: Prospect Letters, 1983-1987 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Membership: Prospect Letters, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Membership: Prospect Letters, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Membership: Prospect Letters, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Membership: Prospect Letters, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Membership: Prospect Letters, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Membership: Prospect Letters, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Membership Renewals, 1987-1991 (Box 8, Folder 1a)
  - Membership Renewals, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 1b)
  - Membership Renewals, Jan 1995 (Box 8, Folder 1c)
  - Membership Renewals, Feb 1995 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Membership Renewals, Mar 1995 (Box 8, Folder 2a)
  - Membership Renewals, Apr 1995 (Box 8, Folder 2b)
  - Membership Renewals, May 1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Membership Renewals, Jun 1995 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Membership Renewals, Jul 1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Membership Renewals, Aug 1995 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Membership Renewals, Oct 1995 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Membership Renewals, Nov 1995 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Membership Renewals, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Membership Reports, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Membership Reports, 1988-1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Membership Reports, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Membership: Withdrawals and Lapsed, 1983-1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Membership: Withdrawals and Lapsed, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Memos, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Memos, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Memos, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Memos, 1980-1985 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Memos, 1986-1989 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Memos, 1990-1994 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Memos, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Memos, 2008, Undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Mentor Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Metropolitan Transportation Authority - Construction Industry Working Group, 2000-2006 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Metropolitan Transportation Authority - Construction Industry Working Group, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Metropolitan Transportation Authority - Construction Industry Working Group: Agendas, 2000-2007 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - New York Building Foundation: Annual Report, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - New York Building Foundation: Board of Governors, 2007-2008 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - New York Building Foundation: Board of Governors, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - New York Building Foundation: Board of Governors: Agendas, 2000-2007 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - New York Building Foundation: Board of Governors Membership Directory, 2009-2010 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - New York Building Foundation: Construction Site Improvement Project, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - New York Building Foundation: Construction Site Improvement Project: Sidewalk Sheds Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - New York Building Foundation: Executive Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Nominating Committee, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Nominating Committee, 1981-1986 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Nominating Committee, 1988-1991 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Nominating Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Nominating Committee, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Nominating Committee, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Nominating Committee, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Nominating Committee, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Nominating Committee, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Organization Chart (NYBC) [additional copy in oversize box 23], 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Personnel Policy Subcommittee, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Pictures of Past Presidents, Correspondence re:, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Policy Guidance: Response Sheets, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Policymaking Committee, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Procurement Policy Committee, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Program Committee, 1924 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Program Committee, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Program Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Public Agency Council, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Public Agency Council, 1999-2004 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Public Building Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Public Building Committee, 2004-2006 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Public Building Committee, 2007-2009 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Public Building Committee: Agendas, 2002-2007 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Public Construction Task Force, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Public Procurement Committee, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Public Procurement Committee, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Public Procurement Committee, 2001-2008 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Public Procurement Committee: Agendas, 2003-2006 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Public Relations: Wachsman Proposal, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Publication Committee, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Reorganization Committee, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Research Project Advisory Board, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Schaffner, Charles (President), 1970-1982 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Search Committee, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Seasonal Operations Committee: "Seasonal Employment in the Building Trades", 1922 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Seasonal Operations Committee: "Seasonal Employment in the Building Trades", 1930 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Special Committee on Hod Hoists and House Cars, 1926, Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Standards Committee: Standard Specifications, 1929, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Strategic Planning Committee, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Task Force on Construction Costs, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Tight Money Committee, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Trans Hudson Express Tunnel Project, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Transportation and Infrastructure Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Transportation and Infrastructure Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Transportation and Infrastructure Committee, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Transportation and Infrastructure Committee, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Transportation and Infrastructure Committee, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Transportation and Infrastructure Committee, Undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Transportation and Infrastructure Committee: Agendas, 2000-2007 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - United States Green Building Council, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Waterfront Development Council, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - "West-Fair" Decision: Task Force, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Series III: General Files, 1918-2011
  Series III: General Files, 1918-2011 contains correspondence, publications, clippings, and other records. Material is mainly organized into subject files, notably on the New York City Building Code and charter revisions.
  - 42nd Street Development Project: Final Environmental Impact Statement (FEIS), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - "1929 Amendments to the New York State Lien Law" (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Air Pollution Control, 1954-1966 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Air Pollution Control, 1970-1977 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - American Consulting Engineers Council, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - American Federation of Labor: Building and Construction Trades Bulletin, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - American Federation of Labor: Building Trades Department, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - American Institute of Architects: Founding History, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - American Institute of Architects: Suggested Guide to Bidding Procedure, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Articles (NYBC), 1980-1995 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Articles (NYBC), 2007, Undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Asbestos Control, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Asbestos Control: Safe Buildings Alliance, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Asbestos Control: Westat, inc. Report, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Asbestos Regulations, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Associated Builders and Contractors, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Associated Builders and Contractors: Press Release, Undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Associated Builders and Owners of Greater New York: Anniversary Invitation, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Associated General Contractors of Minnesota (Pamphlet), Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Barney, William Joshua: Address before New Jersey Building Congress, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Biographical: A-C, Various (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Biographical: D-F, Various (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Biographical: G-H, Various (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Biographical: I-L, Various (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Biographical: M-N, Various (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Biographical: O, Various (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Biographical: P, Various (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Biographical: R, Various (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Biographical: S, Various (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Biographical: T, Various (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Biographical: U, Various (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Biographical: V, Various (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Biographical: W, Various (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Biographical: Z, Various (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Brennan, Peter, 1971-1975 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Building and Construction Trades Council, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Building and Construction Trades Council: Howard McSpedon Memorial, circa 1957 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Building Code, National, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Building Code, New York City, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Building Code, New York City, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Building Code, New York City: Charter Amendment, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Building Code, New York City: Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Building Code, New York City: Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Building Code, New York City: Correspondence, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Building Code, New York City: Correspondence, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Building Code, New York City: Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Building Code, New York City: Committee to Study Article L-1, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Building Code, New York City: Industry Advisory Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Building Code, New York City: Industry Advisory Committee, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 34)